export default [
	{
		date: "4/12",
		question: "Tell me what the Devil’s Dictionary defines as the Hider factor in the progress of the human race.",
		answer: "Villains"
	},
	{
		date: "4/19",
		question: "Between A and B ... which line seems longer ...?",
		answer: "They’re the same"
	},
	{
		date: "4/23",
		question: "Between music, theater, and chariot racing, which sport did Nero win when he participated in the Olympics?",
		answer: "All of them"
	},
	{
		date: "4/25",
		question: "What does the phrase \"My country right or wrong\" mean to convey?",
		answer: ["You unquestionably support it", "You have a duty to correct it"]
	},
	{
		date: "4/27",
		question: "Do you know the name of the theorem named after this number?",
		answer: "Four color theorem"
	},
	{
		date: "4/30",
		question: "First off, the \"wunder\" part probably means ...?",
		answer: "Wonder"
	},
	{
		date: "4/30",
		question: "Next, the \"kind\" part. That’s probably ...",
		answer: "Child"
	},
	{
		date: "4/30",
		question: "Yeah, that’s gotta be it. \"Kind\" means a child ... or at least a young guy, in your case",
		answer: "A prodigy"
	},

	{
		date: "5/7",
		question: "So what’s the literal translation of the phrase \"femme fatale?\"",
		answer: "Fatal woman"
	},
	{
		date: "5/10",
		question: "You know the time period Yoshitsune was active in, don’t you?",
		answer: "The Heian period"
	},
	{
		date: "5/11",
		question: "What historical figure inspired \"favoring the magistrate?\"",
		answer: "Minamoto no Yoshitsune"
	},
	{
		date: "5/11",
		question: "Yoshitune had a brother, right. Oh, I think his name was ...",
		answer: "Minamoto no Yoritomo"
	},
	{
		date: "5/11",
		question: "But they ended up coming into conflict. And in the end when they had to oppose each other ...",
		answer: "Yoritomo won"
	},
	{
		date: "5/11",
		question: "That’s probably because people tend to sympathize less with people in power, and sympathize more with ...",
		answer: "The weak</li>"
	},
	{
		date: "5/12",
		question: "Which brain function is responsible for the phenomenon of seeing an illusion in this figure?",
		answer: "Cognition"
	},
	{
		date: "5/12",
		question: "Which of the following maps can you paint without any adjacent areas being the same color?",
		answer: "Both"
	},
	{
		date: "5/13",
		question: "Name that book that defined \"male factor\" as the chief factor in the progress of the human race.",
		answer: "The Devil’s Dictionary"
	},
	{
		date: "5/13",
		question: "What character archetype refers to a mysterious and seductive woman, typically with ulterior motives?",
		answer: "Femme Fatale"
	},
	{
		date: "5/16",
		question: "What do we call the phenomenon where believing in a treatment’s power is enough to improve your condition?",
		answer: "The Placebo effect"
	},
	{
		date: "5/19",
		question: "Which famous artist of the Edo period is said to have moved residence over 100 times?",
		answer: "Katsushika Hokusai"
	},
	{
		date: "5/21",
		question: "The golden ratio is 1:1.618 but do you know the silver ratio?",
		answer: "1:1.414"
	},
	{
		date: "5/23",
		question: "If we think about what these words have in common, then maybe \"syn\" means ...",
		answer: "Together"
	},
	{
		date: "5/23",
		question: "And \"aisthesis,\" huh? That’s a little like the word aesthetics. I wonder if it means ...",
		answer: "Senses"
	},
	{
		date: "5/23",
		question: "So that means the full word basically means...",
		answer: "Senses coming together"
	},
	{
		date: "5/26",
		question: "Do you know which author Leblanc borrowed from?",
		answer: "Arthur Conan Doyle"
	},
	{
		date: "5/31",
		question: "Do you know which peg-legged, parrot toting historical figure’s appearance became visual shorthand for pirates?",
		answer: "John Silver"
	},
	{
		date: "6/4",
		question: "What do you think the name for the phenomenon is?",
		answer: "The halo effect"
	},
	{
		date: "6/7",
		question: "The red king crab is biologically related to the hermit crab. So how is it different from a crab. Do you know?",
		answer: "The number of legs"
	},
	{
		date: "6/8",
		question: "Where does totalitarianism take things a step further than authoritarianism?",
		answer: "Controlling Public Thought"
	},
	{
		date: "6/13",
		question: "What color do you think it turns (when washing your hair with copper)",
		answer: "Green"
	},
	{
		date: "6/15",
		question: "Between paper bills and coins, which one is issued by the government?",
		answer: "Coins"
	},
	{
		date: "6/20",
		question: "One of these has minor metals in it, right?",
		answer: "Smartphone"
	},
	{
		date: "6/23",
		question: "Now do you know what this woman’s position was?",
		answer: "A pope"
	},
	{
		date: "6/27",
		question: "Which of these animals is involved in an English idiom about the weather?",
		answer: "Dogs"
	},
	{
		date: "6/29",
		question: "What do you think it says on the back of this (Shogi) piece?",
		answer: "Gold"
	},
	{
		date: "7/1",
		question: "What’s the meaning of the original Chinese phrase that these dumplings’ name came from?",
		answer: "Barbarian’s Head"
	},
	{
		date: "7/4",
		question: "Two people are responsible for July and August having 31 days. Do you know who those people are?",
		answer: "Julius and Augustus"
	},
	{
		date: "7/7",
		question: "So Tanabata’s about gods crossing a starry sky to reunite once every year. It might have something to do with... ?",
		answer: "The Milky Way"
	},
	{
		date: "7/7",
		question: "Traditional food",
		answer: "Soumen’s noodles"
	},
	{
		date: "7/9",
		question: "Do you know what shape it is?",
		answer: "A triangle"
	},
	{
		date: "7/11",
		question: "What is long-term memory, anyway?",
		answer: "Memories that last a long time"
	},
	{
		date: "7/11",
		question: "Markus mentioned something about the amount of memories you could store, right? Something like ...",
		answer: "Infinite"
	},
	{
		date: "7/11",
		question: "If you have theoretically infinite space for them... Theoretically, you’d be able to retain them for ...",
		answer: "Forever"
	},
	{
		date: "7/12",
		question: "Do you know what he did?",
		answer: "Thievery"
	},
	{
		date: "7/13",
		question: "If angle C is 28 degrees, and angles A and D are 88 degrees, what is the angle of B and E?",
		answer: "64 degrees"
	},
	{
		date: "7/13",
		question: "I think this came up in class. They were invented by the campus’s guy from Romance of the Three Kingdoms, right?",
		answer: "Zhuge Liang"
	},
	{
		date: "7/13",
		question: "And they were offering something to quell the river ...",
		answer: "Barbarians’ heads"
	},
	{
		date: "7/13",
		question: "This master strategist came up with the baozi to",
		answer: "To offer them instead of heads"
	},
	{
		date: "7/14",
		question: "What is the name and genus of this organism?",
		answer: "Red King Crab (Paralithodes)"
	},
	{
		date: "7/14",
		question: "What happened when the government issued paper and hard currencies in Japan for the first time?",
		answer: "It caused confusion in the economy"
	},
	{
		date: "7/15",
		question: "What is the English equivalent of the Norwegian idiom \"raining witches?\"",
		answer: "Raining cats and dogs"
	},
	{
		date: "7/15",
		question: "Which of the following is another name for spikenard noodles traditionally eaten in Tanabata?",
		answer: "Demon guts"
	},
	{
		date: "9/3",
		question: "Each hand in this famous statue means something, but ... do you know what the right represents?",
		answer: "Prosperity"
	},
	{
		date: "9/6",
		question: "Do you know the name of that phenomenon where the second hand looks like it’s stopped moving?",
		answer: "Chronostasis"
	},
	{
		date: "9/14",
		question: "What does a pawn shop offer that a secondhand shop doesn’t?",
		answer: "Money loans for collateral"
	},
	{
		date: "9/17",
		question: "What’s one of the supposed origins for the phrase \"cat got your tongue?\"",
		answer: "Cats eating human tongues"
	},
	{
		date: "9/21",
		question: "Robot comes from a word in Czech ... but where in Europe is the Czech Republic located?",
		answer: "Central Europe"
	},
	{
		date: "9/24",
		question: "How many white and black shapes are there respectively on a soccer ball?",
		answer: "20 white, 12 black"
	},
	{
		date: "9/28",
		question: "So \"PVS,\" referring to when you mistakenly think your phone is going off... What's the P?",
		answer: "Phantom"
	},
	{
		date: "9/28",
		question: "The next part is the V part. That means it'd be \"phantom...\" what?",
		answer: "Vibration"
	},
	{
		date: "9/28",
		question: "Last is the S. So if we have \"phantom vibration\" so far...?",
		answer: "Syndrome"
	},
	{
		date: "9/29",
		question: "But the fishermen of Nagaragawa are actually civil servants as well. So, tell me which sector they belong to.",
		answer: "Imperial Household Agency"
	},
	{
		date: "10/3",
		question: "If we use \"three watermelons in the sun\" to visualize a certain matter’s size against the universe’s, what are the melons?",
		answer: "Stars"
	},
	{
		date: "10/6",
		question: "Now, do you know who invented this instrument? (Guillotine)",
		answer: "Joseph-Ignace Guillotine"
	},
	{
		date: "10/11",
		question: "Which name was most commonly ascribed to shape B?",
		answer: "Bouba"
	},
	{
		date: "10/17",
		question: "Counting both black and white surfaces, how many surfaces are there in total on a soccer ball?",
		answer: "32 surfaces"
	},
	{
		date: "10/17",
		question: "Didn’t the teacher say that the number of colors used to be different? Do you remember?",
		answer: "It used to be one color"
	},
	{
		date: "10/17",
		question: "Oh yeah, I remember. I think she said that unlike now, soccer games were broadcast with ...",
		answer: "Black and white picture"
	},
	{
		date: "10/18",
		question: "Who conducted executions using this device?",
		answer: "Charles-Henri Sanson"
	},
	{
		date: "10/18",
		question: "What is the reason that most people can not become a commercial fisherman of Nagarasawa?",
		answer: "It’s a hereditary profession"
	},
	{
		date: "10/19",
		question: "What is the meaning of \"robota,\" the etymological root of \"robot\"?",
		answer: "Slave labor"
	},
	{
		date: "10/19",
		question: "Which of the following describes the density of the stars in outer space?",
		answer: "3 bees in all of Europe"
	},
	{
		date: "10/22",
		question: "Now, tell me the total count for each column in this magic square.",
		answer: "15"
	},
	{
		date: "10/24",
		question: "From a psychological standpoint, what’s a key reason our memories can differ from reality?",
		answer: "Memory Bias"
	},
	{
		date: "11/2",
		question: "Can you tell me the meaning of the word \"wack\" in Thieves’ Cant?",
		answer: "A share of stolen goods"
	},
	{
		date: "11/4",
		question: "Clubs is a club, diamond is a gem, so what does a spade represent?",
		answer: "A sword"
	},
	{
		date: "11/8",
		question: "Tell me how old you have to be to listen in on a trial?",
		answer: "Any age"
	},
	{
		date: "11/10",
		question: "Do you know why it’s missing in the character for crow?",
		answer: "Crow eyes are hard to see"
	},
	{
		date: "11/12",
		question: "I wonder. Do you know why voices sound so different over the phone?",
		answer: "Because the voice is synthetic."
	},
	{
		date: "11/14",
		question: "Tell me why that is? (Sun rising over Mt. Fuji)",
		answer: "Because of high altitude"
	},
	{
		date: "11/15",
		question: "He was to be paraded through the city and punished in a very particular way. How was he punished? (Nezumi Kozo)",
		answer: "His head was put on display"
	},
	{
		date: "11/17",
		question: "Do you know the name for this graph? Your hint is \"snails\" ...",
		answer: "Cochleoid"
	},
	{
		date: "12/20",
		question: "Choose the graph which is named after the Chinese yoyo known as a diabolo.",
		answer: "D"
	},
	{
		date: "12/20",
		question: "He was a really famous thief in the Edo period, right? How much money did he steal, in the end?",
		answer: "Over one billion yen"
	},
	{
		date: "12/20",
		question: "As a result he was sentenced to ...",
		answer: "Having his head displayed"
	},
	{
		date: "12/20",
		question: "Criminals, especially famous criminals, were mostly parades around for ...",
		answer: "A performance"
	},
	{
		date: "12/21",
		question: "Which suit of cards represents the Holy Grail?",
		answer: "Hearts"
	},
	{
		date: "12/21",
		question: "According to Japanese judicial law, what is possible for even an infant to do in court?",
		answer: "Attend"
	},
	{
		date: "12/22",
		question: "What country refers to a person who controls politics behind the scenes as a \"prime minister in black?\"",
		answer: "Japan"
	},
	{
		date: "12/22",
		question: "The Japanese word \"dokyuu\" translates to \"massive.\" What English word inspired the initial \"do\" in dokyuu?",
		answer: "Dreadnought"
	},
	{
		date: "1/11",
		question: "What’s this phrase supposed to illustrate about the gods of Shinto?",
		answer: "How numerous they are"
	},
	{
		date: "1/11",
		question: "What’s the phrase again? The one about how many gods there are in Shinto?",
		answer: "The Eight Million Gods"
	},
	{
		date: "1/14",
		question: "Where do you think the fictional land of \"Ihatov\" is modeled after?",
		answer: "Iwate"
	},
	{
		date: "1/18",
		question: "What did the word awful originally mean?",
		answer: "Impressive"
	},
	{
		date: "1/20",
		question: "Do you know what she’s stepping on?",
		answer: "A snake"
	},
	{
		date: "1/24",
		question: "What does that mean when describing a person? (Sweet)",
		answer: "Kind-hearted"
	},
	{
		date: "1/24",
		question: "So what kind of connotation would \"salty\" have in that context?",
		answer: "Negative"
	},
	{
		date: "1/24",
		question: "So with all of that in mind, \"salty\" probably means ...",
		answer: "Resentful"
	},
	{
		date: "1/27",
		question: "How far did this study suggest personal happiness can spread?",
		answer: "To friends of friends of friends"
	}
]
